So, two words and surviving the first game... Now, the next game is...
The second round is a speech recognition game.
This is a game using your smartphone's speech recognition. If you pronounce a picture word and successfully get the word, you're OK.
The correct smartphone English recognition level is set to "native," so you have to pronounce it like a native speaker.
By the way, the answer order is this. Two successful attempts and you win.
Let's hear the first question.
Go ahead.
Here.
This one, right?
Is it...?
This one, you see...
It doesn't recognize it unless it's like a native speaker.
Say it like a native speaker.
Then, let's go.
Go ahead.
Girl.
Coat.
What are we going to do?
Go ahead.
Girl.
It's Cal again!
You're going!
It means it's reaching the ears of a native speaker.
Girl.
You're going.
Native speakers...
Everyone's like that.
Until now, everyone has managed to introduce God.
GIRL
Amazing!
Wow!
It's a native speaker, you know.
Make a hole at the tip of your tongue.
GIRL
Because yours is saying "God," you see.
The second question is this rhythm.
Rhythm.
Rhythm hat.
You're completely missing the "hat" in "rhythm."
A little more...
It's something like a talking hat.
Boak boak.
Rhythm.
Legoma.
It's Cal again!
Amazing!
Cheap!
Wrong.
Two got it right.
GIRL is eliminated.
Well then, let's try in three minutes.
The next question is this.
Rock and roll.
Rocking rocking.
Can you get it?
The answer is a song Bus likes.
A song by an overseas artist.
Rocking rocking.
Looking rocking.
Look at me now.
Racking racking
I don't understand.
Eltoal's, you know.
Racking racking
Jitachaia
Rule stem
Amazing!
I said it with conviction, but I completely missed.
Embarrassing guy
Rule change here.
Because the correct answer rate is too low,
The next person to answer correctly will advance.
And the question is this curry.
Curry
Good job everyone.
This appearing means you've come a long way.
Curry
Good job.
It's coming out on the K side.
You thought you got it just now, right?
Close.
Curry
Oh!
Case
Check
Oh!
Amazing!
With the leg ramen members all wiped out,
Let's go straight to the final showdown.
The final is, as expected, these two.
The game we'll be playing here is
The Complex Guessing Game.
Oh!
This game is
a new game where you take turns stating each other's complexes
in English,
and whoever guesses their opponent's answer first wins.
If you don't answer quickly,
you'll end up insulting each other endlessly.
Team group
We're not winning.
We're not winning, are we?
Even if you say it,
it's over.
When you tell someone about a game you hate,
you should open up then.
Check's, I'm King Comp.
Impressive.
I let it slip a little.
Your mutual complexes
Akabos's complex is exactly
This one.
This is difficult.
Difficult.
Surprisingly, not everyone agrees.
I understand, I understand now.
Not quite.
One step
Meshirata's complex is
What is it?
I can't see it.
It's there.
Really?
Why did you do that kind of thing?
No, no.
Then let's go one by one in turn.
The challenger is Mesurakamto.
Now, your complex in English, please.
Huh?
Then, Funnies is
Debut card
of
Very good.
Japanese
Heytor
I only have one dimple.
That makes it rare.
No, I don't have both.
Having only one is a complex for me.
I think that's just how it is.
This guy only has one.
I hate this, do this instead!
No, no, no!
Well then, a little hint.
First,
Hirata-san's complex is...
His appearance.
Because I'm going to Hirata...
Thinking it's one color...
I'm sorry.
Yes.
You're all taking out the Himetan Beam.
It's close, but...
Look!
Everyone's operating the Himetan Beam.
It's close.
Teacher!
The hint is this.
Something is...
Too big.
Katakaba.
It's probably Katakaba.
Colorful.
No.
But,
It feels like they think like this.
By the way,
His girlfriend's...
To give a hint,
As a human being,
That kind of inner...
A certain spirited aspect comes into play, right?
OK.
You don't have a lot of friends.
Friends...
You have few friends.
That's why I always thought of Hirata-san.
Having few friends...
This beam means you have few friends.
That's right.
Gradually...
This game is over.
If we continue any further,
It seems like we'll reach a situation where we can't bear to look at each other, so
We'll end here.
So,
This time, these two people...
Finally,
Let's all sing the assigned song.
I'm a flower.
I'm a flower
Easy
What I studied today
Didn't stick at all