Two words and surviving the first game... now, the next game is...
The second round is a voice recognition game.
This is a game using your smartphone's voice recognition.  If you pronounce the picture word correctly, you're OK.
The smartphone's English recognition level is set to "native," so you have to pronounce it like a native speaker.
By the way, the answer order is this. Two successful attempts and you win.
Let's hear the first question.
Please.
Here.
This one, right?
Is it...?
This one, you see...
It doesn't recognize it unless it sounds like a native speaker.
Say it like a native speaker.
Let's go then.
Please.
Girl.
Coat.
What are we going to do?
Please.
Girl.
It's "girl" again!
You're up.
It means it didn't register to a native speaker's ear.
Girl.
You're up.
Native speakers...
Everyone's the same.
Everyone here has managed to introduce a god.
GIRL
Amazing!
Wow!
It's gotta be native-sounding.
Making a hole on the tip of your tongue...
GIRL
Because everyone's saying "god," right?
The second question is this rhythm.
Rhythm.
Rhythm hat.
You're not getting the "rhythm hat" at all.
A little more...
It's a talking hat.
Bawk bawk.
Rhythm.
Legoma.
It won't work, will it?
Amazing!
Wrong.
Two failed attempts.
GIRL is out.
Let's try with a 3-minute challenge.
The next question is this.
Rock and roll.
Rocking rocking.
Can you get it?
The answer is a song a bus loves.
A song by a foreign artist.
Rocking rocking.
Looking looking.
Look at me.
Rocking rocking.
Racking racking
It's Eltoal's turn.
It's Kubetz's turn.
Everyone failed.
Let's try challenging Imis's condition.
Racking racking
Jitachaya
The rule's stem
I said it with great conviction, but...
You were totally right.
That's embarrassing.
Rule change here.
Because the correct answer rate is too low,
The next person to answer correctly will win.
And the question is this curry.
Curry
"Good job" is a good job.
The fact that this comes out means you're doing well.
Curry
Good job.
K's side is going to come out.
You thought you got it just now, right?
It was close.
Curry
Wow
That's amazing.
With the leg ramen members all wiped out,
Let's go straight to
the final battle.
Yes.
The final match is, of course,
these two.
The game we'll be playing here is
the Complex Atty Game.
This game is
a new game where you take turns stating each other's complexes in English,
and the first person to guess the other's answer wins.
If you don't answer quickly,
you'll end up talking bad about your opponent forever.
Team, Gzerop?
It's different because
It's unfair.
That's why you should say it properly.
Even with this,
Even if you say it,
Yes, it's called Oshimaimai.
Toys...
When you say "a game someone hates,"
you should open it then.
Of course, I'm King Comp.
Toys...
I said it.
What are your mutual complexes?
Akamon's complex is
Exactly
Difficult
Everyone agrees, right?
Everyone agrees now, right?
I see, I see.
On the other hand, Meshiratar's complex is?
What is it?
Invisible.
It exists.
Really?
Were you laughing when you saw Noujon and thought you'd go for it?
No, no.
Let's go one by one in turn.
The first one is Mesurakamon
Part-time job
Please say "complex" in English.
Huh?
Japanese
Diaphanies
What will open next time?
What will open next?
I only have one dimple.
And I'm self-conscious about it.
No, it's because I don't have both.
Only having one is my complex.
That's the thing about it.
This one, I only have one.
I hate this, I hate this.
No, no, no.
Then, a little hint.
First,
Hirata-san's complex is
Appearance.
Namagos-san's complex is
More like, feelings about games.
Yes, that's right.
Huh
Galley can
The cat is
Hiroi
The cat is Hiroi
This is also Hiroi
No, this
Slight
I thought I was one color from Hiroi.
I'm sorry, not that much.
Never mind the excuses.
It's totally in a month.
Everyone sees the Himetan beam.
It's close, but
Everyone is
Drawn to the Himetan beam.
Sensei
The hint is this.
Let's go to the hint.
Something is
Too big.
Two bake
Katakaba
But, it feels like they think this way.
By the way, Karojo's
To give a hint,
As a human being,
That kind of inner
One spirited minute comes, right?
Ah, OK.
You don't have a lot of friends.
Gutsdar
Ah, friends
I don't have many friends.
So, the hint every time is
First, this
With this beam,
I don't have many friends.
Gradually,
With this beam,
I don't have many friends.
If we continue any further,
We'll reach a point where we can't look at each other, so
We'll end here.
So this time
These two people
Survivor
Finally, to conclude
Let's all sing the challenge song
I'm a star
Yeah!
It's a star
What we studied today
Didn't amount to anything